Luca Bevilacqua

Linux System Administrator Email: luca@lucab.eu

Phone: +39 - 388 69 86 302

Who I Am

I am a Linux administrator and a FOSS enthusiast with 3+ years of experience and with a background as Windows System Administrator (6+ years). I love to experiment and work with new technologies, facing new challenges and pursuing a continuous self-improvement.

I love learning new languages, reading a lot of books, meeting new people and working to make the world a better place!

Experience

Linux System Administrator @ ICT Managed Services (Aruba spa Group)

Date: September 2016 - Present

Support for managed laaS and PaaS services including:

- customer technical assistance
- incident and service request management
- patch management
- installation and maintenance of applications and infrastructures
- system hardening and system automation
- specialist on duty and call shifts

With the following technologies on a fleet of 1000+ physical and cloud servers:

- CentOS/Redhat 5/6/7
- LAMP stack (Apache, MySQL and PHP)
- Varnish and NGINX (LEMP stack)
- System automation with Ansible
- MySQL and Postgres databases
- Scripting with Bash
- IPVS (LVS and Mon) and HAProxy for load balancing
- VMWare virtualization (vCloud and vCenter)
- Monitoring with Pandora, Influxdb/Grafana and Check MK
- Hosting management with Parallels Plesk
- Streaming management with WowZa and Icecast
- Fortigate and pfSense firewalls

Linux System Administrator at Intesa San Paolo SpA at SORINT.lab

Date: January 2016 - August 2016 (8 months)

Production and UAT server and middleware support for:

- RedHat 5/6/7
- Solaris 10
- AIX
- Murex 3
- IBM WebSphere MQ

- Veritas Cluster Server
- RedHat Corosync/Pacemaker High Availability Cluster
- Autosys

Service Operation Specialist at Deutsche Bank SpA at Sorint.LAB

Date: May 2013 - December 2015 (2 years 8 months)

Perform production support activities on assigned applications, including:

- Incident Management
- Service Request execution
- Release review, deployment and support
- Interfacing with international developer and implementor teams (Service Transition) and coordination of

different groups in order to solve incidents occurring on applications and the configuration items involved

(eg. servers, databases, services, etc.)

- Work primarly on Windows Server 2003, 2008 and Linux/Solaris with Apache and Tomcat application servers.

- Specialist On Duty on the Home Banking application and middleware infrastructure
- Maintainance of documentation concerning applications
- Monitoring applications
- Support teams on Emergency task or technology knowledge
- Support Incident Manager (Problem management)

- Windows/VMWare Technician at Sorint.LAB

Date: February 2013 - May 2013 (4 months)

Deploy manager for UBI banca on Windows systems.

- IT Technician at Virtual Venice srl

Date: May 2011 - August 2012 (1 year 4 months)

Maintenance of servers and desktops computers, especially for:

- Windows Server 2003 and 2008
- Vmware environments

Page 2

- email server like Microsoft Exchange and mDaemon
- Windows Xp, Vista and 7
- networks with switches and routers Cisco and HP, and Zyxel or Sonicwall firewalls

- IT Technician at Insula S.p.A.

Date: August 2008 - December 2010 (2 years 5 months)

Installation and Maintenance of:

- Windows Server 2000, 2003 and 2008
- Active Directory forest

- VmWare vSphere 4
- RedHat Linux servers
- Windows 2000, Xp and Vista desktop computers

I have also followed two projects:

- an IT infrastracture corporate merge, from network to desktops
- hardware assistance for the server farm of the website www.Ramses.it

- Developer /Bug fixer

Date: 2006 - 2008 (3 years)

Developer and Bug Fixer for COBOL programs and SQL scripts as a consultant for Generali SpA

Education and Training

- RHCSA & RCHE Preparation courses

Preparation courses for RHCSA and RHCE done on LinuxAcademy (2016/17)

- ITIL v3 Certification

ITIL® Foundation (v3 – 2011 update) Certificate in IT Service Management (2015)

- CISCO CCNA Course

Complete course on Cisco CCNA (2008)

- ITIS C. Zuccante

Computer Expert Diploma, Information Technology, 1999 – 2004

Languages

- Italian (mother tongue)
- English (B2 professional proficiency)
- German (B1)